For an hour or two. can we just
pretend to be like we were before?
No osman.
I'll leave here. go to
reception. get a room upstairs.
I don't need to think about it.
They don't know coyote like I know him.
We need a break.
So we make one.
Coyote's leaking information.
Code bravo. Don't trust anyone.
Owen. you may have just
found the hole in the boat.
If they do have coyote.
they'll allude to it.
Who knows? You may get that call.
Whoever made the call
knows we can trace it
- no matter what.
- Yes.
Eric zheng huang.
Why is he in London?
Business. Politics.
He's got middle
eastern and African links.
I finally saw the size of the stakes
in the game I'd been dealt into.
China was trying to broker
a secret deal in Sudan.
Anyone who exposed the people involved
would immediately be neutralized.
I need to get rid of someone.
Okay. Approaching the pickup point now.
No red team in sight. Proceed.
It's empty.
Wait. no. no. no. no.
Th-there's something in here.
A photo. A polaroid.
That's a phone number.
9:53. contact made with cossack.
Have you lost a bike?
I did.
I found it.
Is it still in good condition?
Information has a price.
This is an auction. Make a bid.
An auction. Who else is bidding?
Who sets the price?
Make a bid.
How? Who to?
Bidding ends in 24 hours.
How do I bid?
Bidding.
Bidding?
Would they actually sell
him to someone else?
Not necessarily. Could be a method.
I found it.
Yeah. Image matches.
Current bid is $140.000.
There's two bidders.
It could be other parties
or it could be to take raises
off the wall and control the sale price.
Someone has put an American agent
up for sale online.
Fuck that. I'm not playing.
I'll tell the Pentagon
Belarusians have decided to
invade the U.S.. whatever.
Why is cossack being so cautious?
The treasure hunt.
the locker. the polaroid.
the anonymous phone number.
the voice on the end. the damn auction?
If an agency had coyote.
they'd come at us straight.
We've got channels. Why
anonymous go-betweens?
Because someone's
scared we'll identify them.
Why? What are they hiding?
Well. one thing's certain:
This isn't the playbook of the fsb.
Coyote isn't being held by an agency.
Not the Belarusians. not the Russians.
Cossack's working alone.
Guo.
You booked a taxi?
I have errands to run.
I can take you.
Thanks. but the taxi's already on its way.
I cancelled it. And I must ask you
not to leave the hotel unaccompanied.
- Why?
- I'm here to protect you.
Protect? Or control?
I know people who know
osman in Chad. Darfur.
I need to keep you safe.
- This mission is too important...
- you're here to protect me
from my protection?
I'm here to work with them.
You need anything. you call me.
Where did you get that jacket?
What have you done?
Enjoy the Sushi.
I won't dance. Not like this.
CIA operatives are valuable.
It's a bluff.
Even if it is. we can't ignore it.
You find cossack. Then we'll talk.
Mikhail bortnik is first contact.
Cossack's in his circle.
Maybe his boss. Maybe not.
Cossack's experienced.
trained. professional.
Uses unconventional
methods to cover his tracks.
Okay. I'll let him know.
The brits are downstairs.
Is it in the diary?
No. but it's Richardson.
Bring him up.
Get Naomi. I'll be right there.
Decent of you to accommodate
this at such short notice.
Try none.
Our. weekly meeting for
tea and biscuits at Legoland
is coming up. What couldn't wait?
Legoland.
We haven't got a droll
name for this place yet.
How can I help you. Jim?
Kensington park gardens.
What about it?
Come on. I thought we shared toys.
The Chinese are brokering
a peace deal in Sudan.
which will leave them in control
of the horn of Africa for decades.
Eric huang of number 73
Kensington park gardens
is making the sandwiches.
Deputies of general hemedti
and de facto ruler
general fattah al-burhan
in attendance.
We thought you knew all
about it. Your backyard and all.
Do you have anything useful to add
to what we already know
about these ongoing talks?
Is he in?
He's meeting the brits.
- Why? Who?
- Richardson.
James Richardson?
I don't want to put anyone's
nose out of joint here.
but if you did know about these talks.
why wouldn't you want
to share that with us?
This is. as you say. our backyard.
I rather think we ought
to be kept up to speed
by an ally on everything that's happening
on our sovereign soil.
Sorry to barge in like this. Henry.
but they need you in the crisis room.
We don't have one of
those. but then again.
we try to avoid crises
as a matter of policy.
You two know each other?
Hello. Brandon.
James is an old mate.
We served together overseas.
Here's the deal. you
don't say "mate." "bloody."
or "quid." and I promise
not to "take a rain check."
I'll walk you to the elevator.
Don't want me wandering
around unescorted?
Nice catch.
So why does it feel like I just got placed
on a concussion protocol list?
You don't think that
was just sis sharing intel?
"Hey look over there!"
Someone says that. in this business...
You're about to lose your wallet.
Or your life.
What the fuck are you doing?
Come on. I'm up for control next year.
Can't hand me an ace
and expect me not to play it.
Motherfucker. I trusted you.
We all make mistakes.
Don't try to fuck me. Jim.
You mean. after everything
we've been through together?
Afghanistan. Iraq. Syria. Yemen?
You say. "jump." we say. "how high?"
If I do get c. all that changes.
PC-9 zoaf is carried by a
lot of cops and army officers.
It's essentially an Iranian
copy of the sig p226.
not terrible.
Chambers nine mil
parabellum. Safety like a sig.
Worth familiarizing
yourself with everything
you'd come across out there.
especially as you'll be
unarmed at all times.
Because I'm not a spy?
So any shooting situation
will be field-found weapons.
You may also find Iranian
copies of the Browning hi-power.
even old Colt m1911s.
So. Edward.
It's my job.
Finding out secrets.
Edward's nice. The end.
Relationships are impossible.
Choose a civilian. you have to lie.
Choose another spook.
you're both never there.
It's okay. we're just fucking.
Okay.
Wait. did he say it was more?
See? I'm not doing this.
Not doing what?
Running little notes
between lovestruck teenagers.
Who said anyone was lovestruck?
Did he say I was?
Think he is?
So. now. this is a great illustration.
Avoid emotional entanglement.
Entangled?
I'm about to ship out.
Good.
A sailor on shore leave.
Exactly. With one in every port.
- Hello?
- A call for you. - Mr. Lewis. - Who?
A woman. Didn't give a name.
Put her through.
Paul?
I'm here.
Abdel had your jacket.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I was so worried about you.
It was nothing. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You don't sound fine.
I'm basically under house arrest.
Do as they say.
They'll figure out
they've made a mistake.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Look. if anyone hurts you
I can look after myself.
- I missed that.
- What?
Your laugh.
Here you are. mate.
- Who was following you?
- I don't know.
Maybe I'm just paranoid.
Lukashenko steamrolled
his secret service for years.
Hoarding power for
himself. It's created schisms.
Colonel buloychyk did all he could
to thwart lukashenko's plans.
so he got sent to the provinces.
- This man...
- Matskevich.
General matskevich. real
opportunist. not a traitor.
Too much to lose.
Cossack. it's my opinion.
has nothing left to lose.
So. like who?
Novikov.
Retired kgb general.
Still active behind the scenes.
Lived for the kgb till
lukashenko took a dump in it.
- Climbed the ranks.
- Vasminoh.
- The octopus.
- Deep well of intel.
- Born spymaster.
- Old-school.
Trained at lubyanka.
He's 76 years old.
Everything about this was old.
Analog. dead drops. breadcrumb meets.
But are you sure?
No.
Enough to go at him? Yes.
Bidding closes in 25 minutes.
Do a deep dive on novikov.
Hello. I'd like to speak
to the general. please.
- Who is calling?
- His oncologist in London.
Dr. Kemple.
- Dr. Ian kemple.
- One moment. please.
Dr. Kemple? I'll put the general on.
Hello. doctor.
Novikov.
I'm calling about a bike you have for sale.
No questions. hung up.
It's him.
We have cossack.
We start paying kidnappers.
we put a target on everyone's back.
A price on their head.
Our enemy takes off heads for free.
Saving coyote is the priority.
Why does it go up at regular intervals?
I don't think it's about money.
It's a game.
Novikov has lived in the same house
for the last 45 years.
Drives a Mercedes-Benz
he bought 18 years ago.
We're in the laundry.
He's checking to see
if we come out clean.
I can feel it.
It's not about the money.
Well. why does he ask for it?
Pressure.
- To get our attention.
- He's an old guy.
he wants to show he can still mix it.
Still play the game.
All right. so...
How do we let him know
that him we can. too?
Pay the two dollars.
How much?
It's at 1.4 million.
This is a live audio feed
from the computer on
his accountant's desk.
You've received a bank transfer
of 1.4 million from a bank in Switzerland.
Who sent me this transfer?
A company called sun
investors partners limited.
Established this morning.
I called you straight
away. It's a large sum.
We need to declare it.
Can I refuse it?
It's already in your account.
Do you have the number
of the account that made the transfer?
Y... of course.
Send it all back.
To the penny.
Touchdown.
Novikov knows we're serious.
Now we wait for his response.
Dr. Kemple's office.
I'd like to speak to Dr. Kemple. please.
This is general novikov.
Tell martian to get down here.
Yes. of course. One moment.
Novikov's just called his doctor.
- Mr. Novikov?
- Dr. Kemple here.
I wanted to let you know
I'll be in London tomorrow.
I don't believe we have
an appointment scheduled.
You called the other day.
You were waiting for me to confirm.
Did I call you?
Your surgery did.
I arrive tomorrow a little after 12 P.M.
I'm so sorry. my schedule's
completely full all afternoon.
I'm sure you'll find time.
Send a car to city airport.
What? I-I don't understand.
Mr. Novikov. I-I think there
must have been a mix-up.
Take necessary measures.
He guessed we'd
listen to the doctor's line.
He's good.
Yes?
Grandpa's pob.
Novikov's inbound.
I'm on my way.
I'll be 20 minutes.
Going dark.
Hi. I think my student ID got handed in?
- Poppy Cunningham?
- Yes.
You're in luck.
Someone brought it in last night.
- Thank you so much.
- That's all right.
I'll have an Espresso. please.
You are studying at the college?
Yeah.
I. I did two years at lie.
- Nice.
- Best years of my life.
Yeah. my. my scholarship
wasn't renewed.
so I-I never got to finish. but.
my country has... Many problems.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
It broke my heart. but. I'm over it.
I made some good friends
there. you know. and
I had one. what was his name?
Paul.
Paul Lewis.
Do you know him?
He's a teacher.
He's not one of mine.
And an author. Paul Lewis the writer.
I don't know anyone with that name.
Perhaps he doesn't exist.
I have to go. Sorry.
Yeah. have a good one.
I'm so sorry for the delay. sir.
Where the fuck is martian?
- Hello?
- Daddy?
- Whoa.
- Hello?
- Slow down. Poppy
I was calling you. Where are you?
Talk to me. What's happening?
Some guy asked if I knew Paul Lewis.
A black guy.
He was tall. handsome.
He was well-dressed
and he had an accent.
African. I think.
Listen.
I'm getting you an Uber.
Double check the plate.
I'll text it.
Go to your mother's.
Wait for me to call.
I'll talk to you later. okay?
Okay.
Fuck!
Okay. Okay.
Fuck.
He really is on his way. sir.
I'm so sorry.
General.
Thank you for waiting.
- You're sweating.
- I ran.
I was late.
I like people who are fast.
Can you do a deal?
Here. now.
I can. but I need to
know what I'm buying.
Goods or information?
Information.
We can do information as
long as it's guaranteed reliable.
Piotr rybak.
Forty-two years old.
Investment manager.
Also known by your
company alias as coyote.
Goddamn it. He gave up his code name.
I want proof he's alive.
He is alive.
For four
five more days.
I can't give you proof.
Then what can you give me?
You're lost.
I'm your compass.
I know what you want to know.
What do you want?
February 11. 1989.
The vogelsang barracks north of Berlin.
The CIA made recordings.
I want the tape.
February 11. 1989.
Vogelsang barracks just north of Berlin.
This country.
Used to be strong.
Majestic.
An industrial powerhouse.
Now look at it.
A ruin.
Authorized.
Approved.
You have a deal.
Where's coyote?
Samia?
Excuse me.
Samia.
My advice?
Get out.
You're still young.
This game... it's for ghosts.
All the things you love.
Family.
Friends. Lovers.
Country.
You will watch them burn.
All you have to do is keep
being good at your job.
Your drive.
Your will to make sacrifices.
Paul?
Play me the beginning.
Stop the tape.
Look.
Your coyote is weak.
Depressed. On drugs.
He fucked up.
Recruited someone connected
to the Russian mercenaries.
They got his psychiatrist
to mess with his pills.
Coyote didn't spot it.
He was arrested dui.
Except he wasn't.
He was drugged.
They took him to a police station
where a corrupt agent named
bogdan antuyk took him out via
one of the underground tunnels
that link our government buildings.
Then he passed him to the mercenaries
for 20.000 Euros.
Fuck me. The Russians have him.
And that's where your
friend's luck runs out.
Yours. too.
Because that officer
works for general volchok.
You know this man?
Commander of Valhalla.
He's like me.
Kgb to his bones.
So. what does he do
when an American spy falls into his lap?
Sell him back to you?
No.
Because these days. Mr. Volchok
commands a powerful army.
I might say a diabolical outfit.
Special forces. private
military contractors.
ex-convicts.
To win friends in Moscow.
he wraps up your poor
coyote as a present.
Wants to unveil him
when a vip is visiting the front next week.
A CIA agent on a plate.
For his masters.
Maybe even for his president.
Where is coyote now?
Behind enemy lines in Ukraine.
Handover with the fsb
takes place next week.
You want him back?
Move fast.
Fuck.
Get me Langley.
secured line in my office.
Who is that?
Reiner mielke.
Head of the stasi
in east Berlin from 1957 to 1989.
Who's the other voice?
What do you think?
Bad German. Heavy accent. Lisp.
Sounds like a young
kgb goon. I don't know.
Right. Keep going.
Which other of our friends was in Berlin
from late '80s. early '90s?
Who cut his teeth there?
Volchok?
Ding. ding.
Paul. it's me again.
I've tried you a million
times. Where are you?
I came to your hotel but you're not here.
Please call me. I have to...
Hello?
Finally. I've been calling you.
I'm fine.
Did you tell mom?
How did he know that name. dad?
Look. it's fine.
- You're safe.
- I didn't say anything.
How does he know that. dad?
Trust me. it's nothing.
Look. honey. I got to go.
Poppy. I love you.
Thank you for joining us. director.
Mr. Secretary. ma'am.
I'm gonna hold off on thank-yous.
From what I hear. the news is not good.
Our missing agent is in
the hands of the Russians.
He'll soon be in Moscow
where they intend to use
him to maximum effect.
You mean they'll go public.
That's the likely outcome. yes.
Well. the timing of this
couldn't be worse for us.
What's the fallout?
By the time we see
him in front of a camera.
the svr and the fsb will
have worked him over.
He will sing whatever tune they call.
American spies in Ukraine.
black ops on the
ground. this will no longer
be a proxy war.
American boots in their backyard.
Yeah. he'll make it us versus them.
Escalate. rattle the nuclear saber.
maybe even justification to go full alert.
What do I tell the president?
Follow him down to
defcon 1? It's not an option.
We'll have to lean out of
Ukraine. which is all they want.
This could change the
shape of the entire conflict.
Talk to me about quality of intel.
How close is your source to the fire?
Source is. good. close. reliable.
Look. this isn't bad news. It's good.
You want to elaborate on that?
Well. we're saying the
Russians have coyote.
It's not true. Valhalla does.
Those guys are a bunch of cowboys.
Let's make no mistake here.
For the first time since
coyote disappeared
14 days and 20 hours ago.
we know where he is. who's holding him.
This is our ball.
So you think you can still get him back?
Yes.
Right?
That's correct. ma'am. yes.
We-we have a closing window
before he's to be handed
over to Russian forces proper.
- How long?
- Four days.
I don't want the president briefed
that he doesn't have a problem here.
He won't. once we get coyote back.
Yeah. if you get him back.
Something London station
has so far failed to do.
We'll find him. we'll get him back.
Bosko. call me now.
We need to talk.
You ever heard about
managing expectations?
You know what we do differently here
than they do in any other
part of the government?
What's so special about
our particular agency?
- Thank you very much.
- We don't go it alone.
- martian.
- You can't think
- in years.
- Procedure's in place
- for a reason.
- We think in decades.
Geopolitical decades. eras.
And that fucking shit up there?
That-that flies five
minutes. and then it's over.
You do not... you do not make
promises you cannot keep.
And if you have a plan. you would think
it would be a good
idea to run it internally
before you go pitching it
straight to the white house
and the dci.
I was playing in the
biggest game of my life.
But I knew something
was about to go wrong.
All I could do was raise the bet.
Fly higher. lie bigger.
Hello? Samia?
Hey. Paul.
Yeah. you are a hard man to find.
You know who was easy to find?
Your daughter. poppy.
But tell me. is it poppy Lewis?
Or poppy Cunningham?
Yeah. I am close. aren't I?
I am very. very close.